{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n10x^3 + 15 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n10x^3 \u003d 10\nx^3 \u003d 1\nx \u003d 1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(10x^3 + 15) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5, -5", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n11x^2 + 14 \u003d 289\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n11x^2 \u003d 275\nx^2 \u003d 25\nx \u003d +/-5", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(11x^2 + 14) \u003d 17", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, -4", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n12x^2 + 4 \u003d 196\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n12x^2 \u003d 192\nx^2 \u003d 16\nx \u003d +/-4", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(12x^2 + 4) \u003d 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, -6", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n6x^2 + 9 \u003d 225\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n6x^2 \u003d 216\nx^2 \u003d 36\nx \u003d +/-6", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(6x^2 + 9) \u003d 15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n14x + 11 \u003d 81\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n14x \u003d 70\nx \u003d 5", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(14x + 11) \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n4x^3 + 21 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n4x^3 \u003d 4\nx^3 \u003d 1\nx \u003d 1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(4x^3 + 21) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\nx^3 + 24 \u003d 1024\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\nx^3 \u003d 1000\nx \u003d 9", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(x^3 + 24) \u003d 32", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n10x + 19 \u003d 49\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n10x \u003d 30\nx \u003d 3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(10x + 19) \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n2x + 1 \u003d 9\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n2x \u003d 8\nx \u003d 4", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(2x + 1) \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n10x^2 + 6 \u003d 16\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n10x^2 \u003d 10\nx^2 \u003d 1\nx \u003d +/-1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(10x^2 + 6) \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n2x + 11 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n2x \u003d 14\nx \u003d 7", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(2x + 11) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n6x^2 + 3 \u003d 9\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n6x^2 \u003d 6\nx^2 \u003d 1\nx \u003d +/-1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(6x^2 + 3) \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n11x + 1 \u003d 100\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n11x \u003d 99\nx \u003d 9", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(11x + 1) \u003d 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n6x^2 + 3 \u003d 9\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n6x^2 \u003d 6\nx^2 \u003d 1\nx \u003d +/-1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(6x^2 + 3) \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7, -7", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n5x^2 + 11 \u003d 256\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n5x^2 \u003d 245\nx^2 \u003d 49\nx \u003d +/-7", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(5x^2 + 11) \u003d 16", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n10x + 4 \u003d 64\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n10x \u003d 60\nx \u003d 6", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(10x + 4) \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\nx^3 + 8 \u003d 16\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\nx^3 \u003d 8\nx \u003d 2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(x^3 + 8) \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, -3", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n12x^2 + 13 \u003d 121\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n12x^2 \u003d 108\nx^2 \u003d 9\nx \u003d +/-3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(12x^2 + 13) \u003d 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n8x + 20 \u003d 100\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n8x \u003d 80\nx \u003d 10", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(8x + 20) \u003d 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, -3", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n9x^2 + 19 \u003d 100\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n9x^2 \u003d 81\nx^2 \u003d 9\nx \u003d +/-3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(9x^2 + 19) \u003d 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n12x + 16 \u003d 100\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n12x \u003d 84\nx \u003d 7", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(12x + 16) \u003d 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, -4", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n3x^2 + 16 \u003d 64\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n3x^2 \u003d 48\nx^2 \u003d 16\nx \u003d +/-4", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(3x^2 + 16) \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, -6", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n13x^2 + 16 \u003d 484\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n13x^2 \u003d 468\nx^2 \u003d 36\nx \u003d +/-6", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(13x^2 + 16) \u003d 22", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n3x + 15 \u003d 36\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n3x \u003d 21\nx \u003d 7", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(3x + 15) \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\nx^3 + 17 \u003d 81\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\nx^3 \u003d 64\nx \u003d 3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(x^3 + 17) \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5, -5", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n14x^2 + 11 \u003d 361\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n14x^2 \u003d 350\nx^2 \u003d 25\nx \u003d +/-5", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(14x^2 + 11) \u003d 19", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n3x^2 + 24 \u003d 36\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n3x^2 \u003d 12\nx^2 \u003d 4\nx \u003d +/-2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(3x^2 + 24) \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n11x + 5 \u003d 49\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n11x \u003d 44\nx \u003d 4", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(11x + 5) \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n4x^3 + 13 \u003d 121\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n4x^3 \u003d 108\nx^3 \u003d 27\nx \u003d 3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(4x^3 + 13) \u003d 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, -4", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n9x^2 + 25 \u003d 169\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n9x^2 \u003d 144\nx^2 \u003d 16\nx \u003d +/-4", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(9x^2 + 25) \u003d 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n15x + 19 \u003d 169\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n15x \u003d 150\nx \u003d 10", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(15x + 19) \u003d 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, -6", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n11x^2 + 4 \u003d 400\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n11x^2 \u003d 396\nx^2 \u003d 36\nx \u003d +/-6", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(11x^2 + 4) \u003d 20", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, -6", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n2x^2 + 9 \u003d 81\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n2x^2 \u003d 72\nx^2 \u003d 36\nx \u003d +/-6", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(2x^2 + 9) \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n5x + 10 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n5x \u003d 15\nx \u003d 3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(5x + 10) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8, -8", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n12x^2 + 16 \u003d 784\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n12x^2 \u003d 768\nx^2 \u003d 64\nx \u003d +/-8", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(12x^2 + 16) \u003d 28", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n4x^2 + 9 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n4x^2 \u003d 16\nx^2 \u003d 4\nx \u003d +/-2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(4x^2 + 9) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\nx + 19 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\nx \u003d 6", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(x + 19) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5, -5", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n3x^2 + 25 \u003d 100\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n3x^2 \u003d 75\nx^2 \u003d 25\nx \u003d +/-5", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(3x^2 + 25) \u003d 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n10x^2 + 9 \u003d 49\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n10x^2 \u003d 40\nx^2 \u003d 4\nx \u003d +/-2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(10x^2 + 9) \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n3x + 1 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n3x \u003d 24\nx \u003d 8", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(3x + 1) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10, -10", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n10x^2 + 24 \u003d 1024\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n10x^2 \u003d 1000\nx^2 \u003d 100\nx \u003d +/-10", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(10x^2 + 24) \u003d 32", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n15x + 9 \u003d 144\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n15x \u003d 135\nx \u003d 9", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(15x + 9) \u003d 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, -4", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n12x^2 + 4 \u003d 196\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n12x^2 \u003d 192\nx^2 \u003d 16\nx \u003d +/-4", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(12x^2 + 4) \u003d 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n14x^2 + 11 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n14x^2 \u003d 14\nx^2 \u003d 1\nx \u003d +/-1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(14x^2 + 11) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n9x^3 + 16 \u003d 4624\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n9x^3 \u003d 4608\nx^3 \u003d 512\nx \u003d 7", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(9x^3 + 16) \u003d 68", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n6x + 13 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n6x \u003d 12\nx \u003d 2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(6x + 13) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, -4", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n4x^2 + 17 \u003d 81\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n4x^2 \u003d 64\nx^2 \u003d 16\nx \u003d +/-4", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(4x^2 + 17) \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5, -5", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n15x^2 + 25 \u003d 400\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n15x^2 \u003d 375\nx^2 \u003d 25\nx \u003d +/-5", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(15x^2 + 25) \u003d 20", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n10x + 4 \u003d 64\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n10x \u003d 60\nx \u003d 6", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(10x + 4) \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n9x + 7 \u003d 16\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n9x \u003d 9\nx \u003d 1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(9x + 7) \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n3x^3 + 22 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n3x^3 \u003d 3\nx^3 \u003d 1\nx \u003d 1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(3x^3 + 22) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n14x + 22 \u003d 36\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n14x \u003d 14\nx \u003d 1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(14x + 22) \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n3x + 4 \u003d 16\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n3x \u003d 12\nx \u003d 4", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(3x + 4) \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n5x^2 + 16 \u003d 36\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n5x^2 \u003d 20\nx^2 \u003d 4\nx \u003d +/-2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(5x^2 + 16) \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n11x^3 + 14 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n11x^3 \u003d 11\nx^3 \u003d 1\nx \u003d 1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(11x^3 + 14) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n2x^2 + 17 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n2x^2 \u003d 8\nx^2 \u003d 4\nx \u003d +/-2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(2x^2 + 17) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n6x + 7 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n6x \u003d 18\nx \u003d 3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(6x + 7) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n4x^2 + 5 \u003d 9\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n4x^2 \u003d 4\nx^2 \u003d 1\nx \u003d +/-1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(4x^2 + 5) \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n6x^2 + 1 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n6x^2 \u003d 24\nx^2 \u003d 4\nx \u003d +/-2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(6x^2 + 1) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8, -8", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n14x^2 + 4 \u003d 900\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n14x^2 \u003d 896\nx^2 \u003d 64\nx \u003d +/-8", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(14x^2 + 4) \u003d 30", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n3x + 22 \u003d 49\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n3x \u003d 27\nx \u003d 9", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(3x + 22) \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n4x + 9 \u003d 49\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n4x \u003d 40\nx \u003d 10", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(4x + 9) \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n7x^3 + 16 \u003d 3600\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n7x^3 \u003d 3584\nx^3 \u003d 512\nx \u003d 7", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(7x^3 + 16) \u003d 60", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n9x + 7 \u003d 16\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n9x \u003d 9\nx \u003d 1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(9x + 7) \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n11x + 11 \u003d 121\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n11x \u003d 110\nx \u003d 10", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(11x + 11) \u003d 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, -3", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n7x^2 + 18 \u003d 81\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n7x^2 \u003d 63\nx^2 \u003d 9\nx \u003d +/-3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(7x^2 + 18) \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7, -7", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n2x^2 + 2 \u003d 100\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n2x^2 \u003d 98\nx^2 \u003d 49\nx \u003d +/-7", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(2x^2 + 2) \u003d 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n12x^3 + 13 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n12x^3 \u003d 12\nx^3 \u003d 1\nx \u003d 1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(12x^3 + 13) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, -4", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n2x^2 + 17 \u003d 49\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n2x^2 \u003d 32\nx^2 \u003d 16\nx \u003d +/-4", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(2x^2 + 17) \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n9x^3 + 9 \u003d 81\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n9x^3 \u003d 72\nx^3 \u003d 8\nx \u003d 2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(9x^3 + 9) \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n11x^2 + 5 \u003d 49\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n11x^2 \u003d 44\nx^2 \u003d 4\nx \u003d +/-2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(11x^2 + 5) \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n2x + 2 \u003d 4\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n2x \u003d 2\nx \u003d 1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(2x + 2) \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n14x + 16 \u003d 100\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n14x \u003d 84\nx \u003d 6", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(14x + 16) \u003d 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n7x^2 + 2 \u003d 9\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n7x^2 \u003d 7\nx^2 \u003d 1\nx \u003d +/-1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(7x^2 + 2) \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n7x^3 + 25 \u003d 81\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n7x^3 \u003d 56\nx^3 \u003d 8\nx \u003d 2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(7x^3 + 25) \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n14x^3 + 22 \u003d 400\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n14x^3 \u003d 378\nx^3 \u003d 27\nx \u003d 3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(14x^3 + 22) \u003d 20", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n5x + 24 \u003d 64\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n5x \u003d 40\nx \u003d 8", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(5x + 24) \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n10x + 6 \u003d 16\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n10x \u003d 10\nx \u003d 1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(10x + 6) \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n10x + 24 \u003d 64\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n10x \u003d 40\nx \u003d 4", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(10x + 24) \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n12x^3 + 21 \u003d 1521\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n12x^3 \u003d 1500\nx^3 \u003d 125\nx \u003d 5", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(12x^3 + 21) \u003d 39", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\nx + 8 \u003d 16\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\nx \u003d 8", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(x + 8) \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n7x^2 + 21 \u003d 49\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n7x^2 \u003d 28\nx^2 \u003d 4\nx \u003d +/-2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(7x^2 + 21) \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, -3", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n12x^2 + 13 \u003d 121\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n12x^2 \u003d 108\nx^2 \u003d 9\nx \u003d +/-3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(12x^2 + 13) \u003d 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n7x^2 + 21 \u003d 49\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n7x^2 \u003d 28\nx^2 \u003d 4\nx \u003d +/-2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(7x^2 + 21) \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n7x^3 + 25 \u003d 900\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n7x^3 \u003d 875\nx^3 \u003d 125\nx \u003d 5", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(7x^3 + 25) \u003d 30", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8, -8", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n14x^2 + 4 \u003d 900\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n14x^2 \u003d 896\nx^2 \u003d 64\nx \u003d +/-8", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(14x^2 + 4) \u003d 30", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\nx^3 + 24 \u003d 1024\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\nx^3 \u003d 1000\nx \u003d 9", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(x^3 + 24) \u003d 32", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\nx + 13 \u003d 16\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\nx \u003d 3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(x + 13) \u003d 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n2x + 15 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n2x \u003d 10\nx \u003d 5", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(2x + 15) \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n11x^3 + 12 \u003d 100\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n11x^3 \u003d 88\nx^3 \u003d 8\nx \u003d 2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(11x^3 + 12) \u003d 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\nx + 1 \u003d 9\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\nx \u003d 8", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(x + 1) \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\nx + 3 \u003d 9\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\nx \u003d 6", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(x + 3) \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n14x^3 + 4 \u003d 900\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n14x^3 \u003d 896\nx^3 \u003d 64\nx \u003d 3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(14x^3 + 4) \u003d 30", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\nx + 2 \u003d 4\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\nx \u003d 2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(x + 2) \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, -3", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n15x^2 + 9 \u003d 144\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n15x^2 \u003d 135\nx^2 \u003d 9\nx \u003d +/-3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(15x^2 + 9) \u003d 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8, -8", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n11x^2 + 25 \u003d 729\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n11x^2 \u003d 704\nx^2 \u003d 64\nx \u003d +/-8", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(11x^2 + 25) \u003d 27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n6x + 7 \u003d 49\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n6x \u003d 42\nx \u003d 7", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(6x + 7) \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n2x^2 + 1 \u003d 9\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n2x^2 \u003d 8\nx^2 \u003d 4\nx \u003d +/-2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(2x^2 + 1) \u003d 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n6x + 16 \u003d 64\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n6x \u003d 48\nx \u003d 8", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(6x + 16) \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "Square both sides of the equation in order to remove the square root.\n3x + 4 \u003d 25\nNow simply solve the equation for x.\n3x \u003d 21\nx \u003d 7", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n√(3x + 4) \u003d 5", "type": "text"}
]}